Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- P
  - Paulson, Arvid, undated (Box 84, Folder 38)
  - Pavel, Misha, undated (Box 84, Folder 39)
  - Paylor, Alfred H., undated (Box 84, Folder 40)
  - Payne, Brittain, undated (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Payne, Donald, undated (Box 84, Folder 42)
  - Payne, E. George, undated (Box 84, Folder 43)
  - Payne, John Collins, 1961, 1968, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 44)
  - Payne, Paul, circa 1938 (Box 84, Folder 45)
  - Payne, William, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 46)
  - Payson, Laurence G., undated (Box 84, Folder 47)
  - Payson, Martin, 1989, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 48)
  - Peabody, Stuart, undated (Box 84, Folder 49)
  - Peach, Lucinda, undated (Box 84, Folder 50)
  - Peale, Norman Vincent, undated (Box 84, Folder 51)
  - Pealman, Howard, undated (Box 84, Folder 52)
  - Pearce, Charles Sprague, undated (Box 84, Folder 53)
  - Pearcy, Frank, undated (Box 84, Folder 54)
  - Pearman, Reggie, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 55)
  - Pearson, Lester Bowles, 1946 (Box 84, Folder 56)
  - Pearson, Noel, undated (Box 84, Folder 57)
  - Pechar, Stanley F., 1960 (Box 84, Folder 58)
  - Peck, Robert S., 1987 (Box 84, Folder 59)
  - Peck, Steven M., undated (Box 84, Folder 60)
  - Peckett, Jack, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 61)
  - Pecora, Joe, circa 1945 (Box 84, Folder 62)
  - Pedhazur, Elazar J., 1976 (Box 84, Folder 63)
  - Pegues, Albert, undated (Box 84, Folder 64)
  - Pekary, Charlotte Helen, 1935 (Box 84, Folder 65)
  - Pell, Claiborne, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 66)
  - Pelletier, Lawrence, undated (Box 84, Folder 67)
  - Penenberg, Adam, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 68)
  - Penrose, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 69)
  - Penzetti, Al, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 70)
  - Peredo, Alfred R., 1964 (Box 84, Folder 71)
  - Perelman, Ron, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 72)
  - Peresich, Mary Giles, 1979 (Box 84, Folder 73)
  - Peres, Maurice, 1959-1960 (Box 84, Folder 74)
  - Peres, Shimon, 1994
    - Photographs (Box 84, Folder 75)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 36)
  - Perkinson, Henry J., 1965, 1984, circa 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 76)
  - Perlin, Ken, undated (Box 84, Folder 77)
  - Perlman, Hyhak, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Perrior, Hector, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Perring, undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Perry, Frank, undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Perry, Nelson, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Perry, Robert M., 1965 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Perry, Stephen, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Pershing, John J., 1925, 1930 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Perullo, Paul, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Peschel, John, 1982, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Peskin, Charles, undated (Box 121, Folder 37)
  - Peslan, Charles, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Petereit, Harry, circa 1937 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Peter the Great, undated (Box 121, Folder 38)
  - Peterfreund, Herbert, 1958, 1964-1968, 1970, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Peters, Francis E., 1980
    - Photographs (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 39)
  - Petersen-Snyder, Christine, undated (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Peterson, Bruce, undated (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Peterson, Eldridge, undated (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Peterson, Rudolph A., 1964 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Peterson, Shirley, undated (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Petit, Frederic-Charles, undated (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Petrie, Milton, 1992 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Petrillo, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Petro, S., 1964 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Petrow, Richard, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Pfeifer, Maxwell, undated (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Pfeiffer, Karl, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Pfund, Niko, undated (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Phelps, Roger P., undated (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Phelps, William Lyon, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Philips, Arthur, 1966 (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Phillips, Arthur C., 1937 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Phillips, Denis S., 1956 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Phillips, Eric, undated (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - Phillips, Michael, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - Phillips, Philip R., 1962 (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - Phillipson, Lennart, 1993 (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Picasso, Pablo, undated (Box 85, Folder 37)
  - Pick, Joseph, undated (Box 85, Folder 38)
  - Pickard, Shem, undated (Box 85, Folder 39)
  - Pickett, Ralph E., 1959 (Box 85, Folder 40)
  - Piez, Gerald, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 41)
  - Pierce, Samuel R. Jr., 1988 (Box 85, Folder 42)
  - Piersa, Robert, undated (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Pierson, Israel C., 1897 (Box 85, Folder 44)
  - Pierson, Willard J., 1966 (Box 85, Folder 45)
  - Pierson, William, undated (Box 85, Folder 46)
  - Pierz, John, 1965-1966 (Box 85, Folder 47)
  - Piffard, H.C., undated (Box 85, Folder 48)
  - Pildes, Richard H., undated (Box 85, Folder 49)
  - Pines, Burt S., 1973 (Box 85, Folder 50)
  - Pines, Hyman, undated (Box 85, Folder 51)
  - Pinkowitz, S., undated (Box 85, Folder 52)
  - Pinochet, Augusto, undated (Box 121, Folder 40)
  - Pinto, Tony, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 53)
  - Pirola, David, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 54)
  - Pisani, Bernard J., 1947, 1964, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 55)
  - Pisani, Joseph M., 1967 (Box 85, Folder 56)
  - Pita, José, undated (Box 85, Folder 57)
  - Pitofsky, Robert, 1964, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 58)
  - Pitt, Frank M., 1971 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Pitt, Levin W., undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Pitti, Donald R., undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Pizzurro, Joseph, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Piasecki, Frank N., 1985 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Platon, Lydia, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Platt, Bob, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Platt, Clara Skiles, undated (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Plentzas, Joe, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Pless Sisters, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Plunkett, Guy D., undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Podell, Albert, undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Podilla, Elena, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Poitier, Sidney, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Polak, Stanley J., undated (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Polakoff, Murray E., 1969 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Poli, Gino, undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Pollack, Judge, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Pollack, Lester, 1965-1993 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Pollack, Thomas C., 1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Pollard, Sam, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Pollack, Merrell, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Polniaszek, Steve, 1977, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Pomerantz, Harold, undated (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Pomeroy, John N., undated (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Pontorino, Edward, undated (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Popkin, Henry, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Poppel, Maxwell, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Porrata, Dolf, 1966, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Porrati, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Porter, David B., 1943 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Porter, Cole, undated (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Porter, Richard, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Porter, Sylvia F., 1985 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - Portnoy, Zamira, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Portuondo, Tina Hestrom, undated (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Posner, Kathleen, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Post, Roy, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Postman, Neil, 1963, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Potter, Jacobus, undated (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Poulos, John, undated (Box 121, Folder 41)
  - Pound, 1957 (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Pound, Roscoe, undated (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Pourbabai, Behnam, undated (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - Povell, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Powell, Charles M., 1961, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 45)
  - Powers, Maxwell, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 46)
  - Prager, George, undated (Box 86, Folder 47)
  - Prager, Jerome, undated (Box 86, Folder 48)
  - Prager, Jonas, undated (Box 86, Folder 49)
  - Prago, Ruth, undated (Box 86, Folder 50)
  - Prater, Charles, undated (Box 86, Folder 51)
  - Prentis, H.W., undated (Box 86, Folder 52)
  - Prentiss, Henry J., undated (Box 86, Folder 53)
  - Press, Dr. Joseph H., 1985 (Box 86, Folder 54)
  - Pressman, Gabe, 1962, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 55)
  - Preyer, Allen T., 1948 (Box 86, Folder 56)
  - Price, Kathleen, undated (Box 86, Folder 57)
  - Price, Leontyne, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 58)
  - Price, Philip, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 59)
  - Price, Reginald, undated (Box 86, Folder 60)
  - Pride, H., undated (Box 86, Folder 61)
  - Prime, John H., 1954, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 62)
  - Primont, Mrs. M.G., undated (Box 86, Folder 63)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 64)
  - Prince, Carl, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 65)
  - Prince, James, undated (Box 86, Folder 66)
  - Pritchard, Norman H., undated (Box 86, Folder 67)
  - Prior, Harris, undated (Box 86, Folder 68)
  - Prior, Karen, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 69)
  - Proctor, Polly, undated (Box 121, Folder 42)
  - Procul, Harum, undated (Box 86, Folder 70)
  - Profeta, Dr. Arnold R., undated (Box 86, Folder 71)
  - Protano, Marco, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 72)
  - Proust, Marcel, undated (Box 121, Folder 43)
  - Pruden, Durward, undated (Box 86, Folder 73)
  - Prunty, Bert S., 1963, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 74)
  - Prusmack, Armand, circa 1937-1939 (Box 86, Folder 75)
  - Prusmack, Jon, undated (Box 86, Folder 76)
  - Puckett, Elizabeth, undated (Box 86, Folder 77)
  - Pugel, Thomas A., 1983, 1999
    - Photographs (Box 86, Folder 78)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 44)
  - Pugliese, Julia Jones, 1941
    - Photographs (Box 86, Folder 79)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 45)
  - Pulley, Andrew, undated (Box 86, Folder 80)
  - Pulley, W.J., undated (Box 86, Folder 81)
  - Pupin, Mihajlo, 1924 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Purrington, William A., 1939 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Putnam, Francis J., 1962, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Putnam, Robert, undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Putney, W. Taylor, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Q
  - Quackenbush, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Quartararo, Ignatus N., 1964, 1967, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Quasla, William H., undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Quigley, John, 1937, 1942 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Quigley, John J., 1925, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Quilter, Dan, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Quilty, Daniel E., undated (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Quinby, Charles E., undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Quinn, Anthony, undated (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Quinn, Janice, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Quinn, Vivian, undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
- R
  - Raab, Ernest L., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Raasch, John E., 1917, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Rabe, Louis H.W., undated (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Rabezak, Stanley Henry, circa 1940-1941 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Rabin, Robert, 1998 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Rabinowitz, Chaim, undated (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Rabins, Michael J., 1969 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Rabkin, Mabel, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Racoosin, Theodore, undated (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Rader, Paul, 1966 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Radnick, Suzanne, undated (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Radosavljevish, Paul R., undated (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Radosta, John, 1967 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Rafig, Marcia, undated (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Ragazzini, John R., 1959, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Rague, Edward, undated (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Ragusa, Isa, undated (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Rainer, Andrew, undated (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Rakin, Lorin, undated (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Rakoff, Allan, undated (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Rakove, Jack, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 37)
  - Ralli, Elaine P., undated (Box 87, Folder 38)
  - Ramakrishna, Mushti, undated (Box 121, Folder 46)
  - Ramsay, William W., 1965 (Box 87, Folder 40)
  - Ramsey, Cal, 1958-1959, 1992-1997 (Box 87, Folder 41)
  - Ramsey, Gloria, 2000 (Box 87, Folder 42)
  - Ramsey, James, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 43)
  - Ramirez, Arnold, 1970 (Box 87, Folder 44)
  - Ramor, Gladys Gonzalez, undated (Box 87, Folder 45)
  - Randall, Tony, undated (Box 87, Folder 46)
  - Rangel, Charles, undated (Box 87, Folder 47)
  - Ranney, Winthrop, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 48)
  - Rapkin, Bruce, undated (Box 87, Folder 49)
  - Rather, Dan, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 50)
  - Raths, Louis, 1959, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 51)
  - Ratliff, Floyd, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 52)
  - Ratliff, James R., 1969 (Box 87, Folder 53)
  - Ravitch, Richard, undated (Box 87, Folder 54)
  - Rawlings, Arthur L., undated (Box 87, Folder 55)
  - Ray, Gordon N., undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Ray, Nick, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Raymo, Robert R., 1974, 1979, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Raynes, Martin J., undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Reagan, Ronald, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Reasoner, Charles, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Recht, Laura, undated (Box 121, Folder 47)
  - Rechtingle, Robert, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Redding, Maxin, 1984, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Reddy, Krishna, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Redefer, Frederick, 1962, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Redlich, Norman, 1964-1987 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Redlich, Norman A., undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Reed, undated (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Reed, Lewis Benedict, 1897 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Reed, Willie, undated (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Reems, Harry, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Rees, Judson M., 1958 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Reese, Gustave, 1972, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Reese, Jesse C., undated (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Reeves, Mildred, undated (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Reevy, Kevin, circa 1987-1988 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Regalado, Nancy, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Rehberg, Charles F., 1963 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Reibal, Heintz, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Reich, Artur M., undated (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Reich, Herman, circa 1934-1936 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Reichel, Arie, undated (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Reid, Helen Rogers, 1944 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Reid, Jean, undated (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Reid, Jean, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Reid, John Phillip, 1984, 1986, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Reid, Keith, undated (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Reid, Ross, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Reimer, Richard, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - Reimers, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Rein, Catherine A., undated (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Reiner, Mark, 1960-1961 (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Reiner, S. Theodore, 1970 (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Reines, Frederick, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Reingold, Suzy, undated (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Reinhold, Walter, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - Reis, Vincent, circa 1934-1935 (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - Reiss, Bonnie, 1993, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - Reiss, Carol S., undated (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - Reiss, Lester, circa 1936-1937 (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - Reiss, Steven, 1984, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 46)
  - Reisser, Otto H., 1961 (Box 88, Folder 47)
  - Reitano, Vincent, 1939-1940 (Box 88, Folder 48)
  - Reithels, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 49)
  - Reither, Joseph, undated (Box 88, Folder 50)
  - Relittle, Lawrence, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 51)
  - Renfrew, Baron (Prince of Wales), undated (Box 88, Folder 52)
  - Rennert, Ira and Inge, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 53)
  - Renshaw, Raemer Rex, undated (Box 88, Folder 54)
  - Rentzepnic, Dionisos, undated (Box 121, Folder 48)
  - Renwick, Fred, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 55)
  - Renzi, George, circa 1936-1937 (Box 88, Folder 56)
  - Repa, Theodore, undated (Box 88, Folder 57)
  - Rethy, Susan, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 58)
  - Rettig, Lena, undated (Box 88, Folder 59)
  - Reuter, John, 1952 (Box 88, Folder 60)
  - Reutman, Gladys E., undated (Box 88, Folder 61)
  - Reutershaun, Oscar, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Revere, John, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Revere, Pauline, 1934 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Revesz, Richard, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds, Albert, 1992
    - Photographs (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 49)
  - Reynolds, Gerald B., 1972, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds, Helen, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds, Jerry, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Rhodes, Larry, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Rhodes, Yorke, 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Rhyme, 1957 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Ribaudo, Guy Gilbert, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Ricci, John E., 1960 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Rice, C. Duncan, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Rice, Eve, undated (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Rice, Theodore D., 1955 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Rice, Tony, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Rich, Adrienne, undated (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Rich, Maurice H., undated (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Rich, Raymond J., undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Richards, Arthur, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Richards, David, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Richards, T. Addison, undated (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Richardson, Hilda, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Richter, Thomas, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Ried, John, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Riemer, undated (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Riesman, Michael, undated (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Riklis, Meshulam, undated (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Rinaldi, Frank J. Jr., 1964 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Rinfret, Pierre, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Rinfret, Thibaudeau, undated (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Ring, Barbara, circa 1990 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Riordan, C. James, 1928 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Risch, Frank, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Ritchie, Anne, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Riter, Seymour, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Ritter, John, undated (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Ritter, Lawrence F., 1964, 1969, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Rittereiser, Robert, undated (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - Rivera, Arnold, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 41)
  - Rivera, Haydee, undated (Box 89, Folder 42)
  - Rivera, Ralph, undated (Box 89, Folder 43)
  - Rizzolo, Richard A., 1985 (Box 89, Folder 44)
  - Roach, James, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 45)
  - Rob, Joan, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 46)
  - Robards, Jason, undated (Box 89, Folder 47)
  - Robbins, Carrie F., 1973, 1978-1979 (Box 89, Folder 48)
  - Robbins, Carril, undated (Box 121, Folder 50)
  - Robbins, Cassie, undated (Box 89, Folder 49)
  - Robbins, Clive and Carol, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 50)
  - Robbins, Fred C., 1895 (Box 89, Folder 51)
  - Robbins, Herbert A., undated (Box 89, Folder 52)
  - Robbins, Jerome, 1995
    - Photographs (Box 89, Folder 53)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 51)
  - Robbins, Lynn, 1983, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 54)
  - Roberto, Joseph J., 1972 (Box 89, Folder 55)
  - Roberts, Anthea, undated (Box 89, Folder 56)
  - Roberts, Archie, undated (Box 121, Folder 52)
  - Roberts, Arthur, 1929 (Box 89, Folder 57)
  - Roberts, Burton, undated (Box 89, Folder 58)
  - Roberts, Cokie, undated (Box 89, Folder 59)
  - Roberts, Erin, undated (Box 89, Folder 60)
  - Roberts, Jenny, undated (Box 89, Folder 61)
  - Robert, Joseph J., 1960 (Box 89, Folder 62)
  - Roberts, Steve, undated (Box 89, Folder 63)
  - Roberston, Horace K., undated (Box 89, Folder 64)
  - Robertson, John, 1957, 1962, 1971 (Box 89, Folder 65)
  - Robertson, Martin L., 1942 (Box 89, Folder 66)
  - Robertson, Tiffany H., undated (Box 89, Folder 67)
  - Robesch, Paul, undated (Box 121, Folder 53)
  - Robeson, Paul and Susan, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 68)
  - Robinson, Beverly, undated (Box 89, Folder 69)
  - Robinson, Blanchard W., 1968 (Box 89, Folder 70)
  - Robinson, Daniel D., 1961, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 71)
  - Robinson, David, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 72)
  - Robinson, Elsa, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, George, 1911 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Jackie, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Robinson, John, 1964, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Robinson, Leland Rex, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Robinson, Mary, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Robinson, Mimsie, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Robinson, Mrs. (with John Sexton), undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, Seymour, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, Stephen, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Robinson, Thomas P., 1955, 1963-1965 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Robinson, William F., undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Robito, Lou, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Robler, Carol, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Roblins, Harold, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Roche, Mary, undated (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Rochelle, Carlton, 1979-1980, 1983, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Rock, Marcia, undated (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Rock, Pat, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Rockefeller, David, undated (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Rockefeller, Laurence, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, undated (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Rockwell, John, undated (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Roddenberry, Gene, 1984 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Roden, Henry, undated (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - Rodgers, Raymond, undated (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Rodgers, Rod and Barbara Roan, undated (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Rodis, Hank, undated (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Rooman, Kenneth, undated (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Rodriguez, Amelia, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Rodriguez, Christina, undated (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Rodriguez, Jose, undated (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Rodriguez, Robert, undated (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Roe, Joseph W., undated (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Roebling, Emily, undated (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Roesner, Edward, undated (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Rogers, Carl, undated (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Rogers, David, undated (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - Rogers, Dolores, undated (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Rogers, Hugo E., 1963 (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Rogers, James, undated (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - Rogers, James, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - Rogers, John Newton, undated (Box 90, Folder 43)
  - Rogers, Martha, 1955, 1958-1959 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - Rogers, Richard, undated (Box 90, Folder 45)
  - Rogoff, Julian, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 46)
  - Rohan, Jack, 1958-1960 (Box 90, Folder 47)
  - Rohrbach, John F.D., 1953 (Box 90, Folder 48)
  - Rohrbaugh, J.H., 1935 (Box 90, Folder 49)
  - Rojo, Marta, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 50)
  - Roland, Sanford J., undated (Box 90, Folder 51)
  - Rom, Dorothy and Irving, undated (Box 90, Folder 52)
  - Roman, Freddie, undated (Box 90, Folder 53)
  - Romano, Roberta, undated (Box 90, Folder 54)
  - Rome, Harold, undated (Box 121, Folder 54)
  - Romer, Judy, undated (Box 90, Folder 55)
  - Romich, Tom, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 56)
  - Ronan, William J., 1953, 1969 (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - Ronstadt, Linda, undated (Box 90, Folder 58)
  - Ronen, Boaz, undated (Box 90, Folder 59)
  - Rooks, Carlton, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 60)
  - Roos, Daniel, undated (Box 90, Folder 61)
  - Roosa, Robert, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 62)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1953-1956 (Box 90, Folder 63)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., undated (Box 90, Folder 64)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. Jr., 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Roosevelt, George Emlen, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Roosevelt, Sara, 1938 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Root, Elihu, 1929 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Rose, Ernst, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Rose, Robert, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Rose, Tricia, undated
    - Photographs (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 55)
  - Rosecrance, Francis C., 1956 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Roselle, Charles, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Rosen, Alex, 1960, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Rosen, M., 1986 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Rosen, Stanley, undated (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Rosen, Sumner, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Rosenberg, Lisa, undated (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Rosenberg, Michael S., 1975 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Rosenberg, Paul, undated (Box 121, Folder 56)
  - Rosenberg, Yale, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Rosenblant, Seymour, circa 1937 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Rosenblatt, Louis, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Rosenblatt, Roger, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Rosenbloom, H. David, undated (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Rosenblum, Robert, undated
    - Photographs (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Negatives (Box 121, Folder 57)
  - Rosenblum, Lucille, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Rosenbluth, Milton B., undated (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Rosencranz, Carlos, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Rosenfeld, Dina, undated (Box 121, Folder 58)
  - Rosenkampff, Arthur H., undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Rosenkampff, Frederick, undated (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Rosenthal, M.L., 1964-1979 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Rosenwald, John, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Roses, Dr. Daniel, undated (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Rosh, Rieva, undated (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Ross, Andrew, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Ross, Benjamin A., 1942-1960 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Ross, Deniss, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - Ross, Donald, undated (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - Ross, Jerrold, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 36)
  - Ross, Kristen, undated (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - Ross, Marvin, undated (Box 91, Folder 38)